aoi hoshi ni senritsu ga hashiru
a
o
i
ho
shi
ni
se
n
ri
tsu
ga
ha
shi
ru
A shudder runs over the blue planet
푸른 지구에 전율이 흐른다
kuroi arashi chikazuku toki
ku
ro
i
a
ra
shi
chi
ka
zu
ku
to
ki
It's the time the dark storm approaches
검은 폭풍이 닥쳐오는 순간
kokoro no oku de mezameru HERO
ko
ro
no
o
ku
de
me
za
ru
HE
RO
It's as if a hero is awakening on the inside
마음 속의 눈을 뜬 영웅들이여
tobitatsu no da furimukazu ni
to
bi
ta
tsu
no
da
fu
ri
mu
ka
zu
ni
Fly away and don't look back!
뒤돌아보지 말고 날아가라
DAGWON kagayake DAGWON
DA
G
WON
ka
ga
ya
ke
DA
G
WON
Yuusha Shirei
Dagwon
Brave Command Dagwon
용자지령
다그온
Dagwon... Shine on!! Dagwon!
다그온 빛나라!! 다그온
heiwa mamoru namae sa
he
i
wa
ma
mo
ru
na
ma
e
sa
The name that protects the peace
평화를 지키는 이름이다
DAGWON oretachi DAGWON
DA
G
WON
o
re
ta
chi
DA
G
WON
Dagwon! We are Dagwon!
다그온 우리는 다그온
yume wa zettai watasanai
yu
me
wa
ze
t
ta
i
wa
ta
sa
na
i
We will never hand over our dream
꿈은 절대로 넘겨줄 수 없다
afureru yuuki te ni shitai nara
a
fu
re
ru
yu
u
ki
te
ni
shi
ta
i
na
ra
To grab the overflowing courage
넘쳐흐르는 용기를 거머쥐고 싶다면
tsuyoku tsuyoku yuujou shinjiru koto sa
tsu
yo
ku
tsu
yo
ku
yu
u
jo
shi
n
ji
ru
ko
to
sa
We believe in our friendship firmly
우리 우정을 굳게 믿는 거다
kizutsuku koto mo osore wa shinai
ki
zu
tsu
ku
ko
to
mo
o
so
re
wa
shi
na
i
We are not afraid of getting hurt
상처입는 것도 두렵지 않아
mugendai no mirai wo egaku sono tame ni
mu
ge
n
da
i
no
mi
ra
i
wo
e
ga
ku
so
no
ta
me
ni
In order to reach that infinite future!
무한대의 미래를 그려내기 위해서라면
It's dangerous like this...
위험해, 이대로는…!
What?!
아니?!
Rai always runs away so fast...
정말, 라이 군은 금새 도망쳐 버린다니까
When are you going to get off him?!
아앗, 언제까지 붙어 있을 거야?!
Get off!
저리 비켜!
Shut up!
시끄러!
He's mine as I found him!
내가 발견했으니까 내 거야!
Now, Rai dear,
자, 라이 군
please respond to my letter today~
오늘은 꼭 편지의 답장을 들려줘
I, I have an important mission!
제, 제게는 중요한 임무가 기다리고 있습니다
S- so...
그, 그러니까…
Help me!
히익;; 살려줘~!
The Ruler of Sargasso
사르갓소의 지배자
Radio Wave Alien Pulse Seijin
Appears
전파 우주인 펄스 성인
등장
Earthlings are even scarier than aliens from Sargasso...
지구인이 사르갓소의 우주인보다 무서운 것 같아…
It was a good idea to wait for you here.
여기에서 기다리고 있던 게 딱 들어맞은 것 같군
Now, let the experiment begin.
자, 실험을 시작하자
Understood...
알았습니다
So that's the seventh Dagwon, Thunder Rai.
저게 일곱 번째 다그온
선더 라이인가…
Brother Mado.
마도 형
Oh, Hido. How does the Earth look?
그래, 히도
지구의 상태는 어떠냐?
It's getting more and more interesting.
점점 더 재미있어질 것 같은걸
Thanks to a half-witted Dagwon recruit.
얼빠진 신인 다그온의 등장으로 말이지
We'll be done soon.
이쪽은 곧 정리된다
We'll send you an interesting playmate soon.
곧 즐거운 놀이상대를 보내줄 테니 기다려라
Please do, brother.
잘 부탁해, 형
You idiots!
어리석은 놈들!
What'll you do? Are you still planning to turn on me?
어쩔 테냐? 너희들, 아직도 덤빌 테냐?!
No matter how many of you are there, I'll take all of you down!
몇놈이든 싸잡아 상대해 주마
You on that side! Still uninterested?
거기 너희들 어떠냐?
Don't make us laugh!
웃기지 마라!
You guys still are prisoners and all. Who will be stupid enough to trust you?
네놈들도 죄수잖아 미쳤다고 네놈들 말을 듣냐?
I thought I killed all the idiots.
아직 바보가 남아있었군
If it isn't Brother Mado?
마도 형
Gedo, how long will you keep playing?
게도, 언제까지 놀고 있을 셈이냐?
I know, bro.
알았어, 형
Understand this!
알겠냐, 자식들아!
As of today, we are the Rulers of Sargasso!
오늘부터 이 사르갓소의 지배자는 우리가다
Your life and death is under our hands.
네놈들이 사는 것도 죽는 것도 모두 우리에게 달려 있다
If you want to survive, then do as we order!
살아남고 싶다면 우리 명령에 따라라!
We are the Three Warugaia Brothers!
우리, 와르가이아 3형제에 말이다!
Alright. We'll start by disposing of the biggest eyesore, those Dagwon punks.
좋아! 우선은 눈엣가시같은 다그온 놈들의 처리다
According to my younger brother Hido on Earth, it seems that a Dagwon recruit has come.
지구에 있는 동생, 히도의 말에 따르면 신입 다그온이 온 것 같다
Would any of you like to go take his neck for a greeting?
누가 인사 대신 그녀석의 목을 따오지 않겠냐?
Leave it to me.
내게 맡겨라…
I have a ha- hatred towards the Space Police Organization...
우주 경찰 기구에는…
워, 원한이 있…
Mado bro...
마도 형…
I heard that Dag Thunder uses thunder as his weapon.
다그 선더는 번개를 무기로 사용한다고 들었다
If then...
그렇다면…
It's your turn, Pulse Seijin.
네 차례다, 펄스 성인
You have an expert's eye to pick me.
날 지명하다니, 안목이 높군
Uh, hey...
저, 저기…
Do we really have to do this here?
정말 여기에서 하는 건가요?
Right. More witness, the better.
그래, 목격자는 많은 편이 좋은걸
Yeah, sure...
할 수 없지
Excellent! My expectations were right!
대단해!
역시 기대한 보람이 있어!
This is definitely psychokinesis!
이거야말로 틀림없는 사이코키네시스!
Are you satisfied?
만족하셨나요?
Then...
그럼, 전 이걸로…
You!
자네~!
That was excellent!
이야~ 자네 정말 대단하구만!
Is it something called super magic?
"초 마술"이란 건가?
This will do good on TV!
이거 잘 나갈 거야, 자네~
Hey! Don't act violently on my test subject!
이봐요! 내 실험 동물을 난폭하게 다루지 말라구요!
Oh, sorry, sorry!
아아, 실례 실례~
I am this kinda person... Here.
나 이런 사람인데, 자…
Igusa TV?
이구사 TV?
Producer?
프로듀서…?
I am taking part in this program.
내가 맡고 있는 방송은 이거, 이거야~
Sunset Kiss?
선셋 키스(Sunset kiss)?
What is that?
뭐예요, 그게?
-Don't you know?
-Yes.
-자네, 정말 몰라?!
-네
That's too bad! It's our variety show.
곤란하구만~
버라이어티 프로라구~
That was expected from Rai's manager!
라이의 매니저가 이래선 안되는데~
I am not a manager!
난 매니저가 아니예요!
Moreover, weren't we going out for a science program?
게다가, 과학 방송에 나가는 게 아니었나요?
No running away!
도망치지마!
That's too bad!
어머나~
A science program with a sly trick? Far from it!
속임수 비스무리한 걸 가지고 난데없이 과학 방송이라니 택도 없지
Also, think about it.
그리고, 잘 생각해 봐
Going out for a variety show is more convenient!
버라이어티 프로에 나가는 편이 나중에 편리하다구
You can easily lie a trick as some superpower!
속임수를 초능력이라고 뻥쳐도 말이지
I do not lie!
전 거짓말 따윈 하지 않아요!
Please shut up!
넌 조용히 해!
Right. Making people know about this is more important.
그래, 우선 사람들에게 알려야겠지
Then...
그럼…
OK! We'll go out!
OK! 방송에 나갈게요~
N-no way!
그. 그럴수가!
Great! It's decided!
좋아, 결정이다!
You'll be at the center of tomorrow's live broadcast!
내일 생방송의 중심으로 하지
Now, we have a rehearsal at 4 tomorrow, so please come. Nice to meet you!
그럼, 내일 4시에 스튜디오에서 리허설이 있으니까 기다릴게~
잘 부탁해~
-Yes!
-W- wait, Ms. Maria!
-네~
-자, 잠깐, 마리아 씨
It'll be alright. I'll go too.
괜찮아, 나도 따라갈 테니까
No, that's not the problem...
아니, 그런 문제가 아니라…
Anyway, would you like to have a tour in this TV station?
그것보다, 이왕 온김에 방송국 견학 안 할래?
Places like this are the center of mysterious phenomenons!
이런 곳이 바로 괴기 현상의 중심지라구~
What am I doing here?
난 대체 뭘 하고 있는 거지…
Do you feel the presence of ghosts?
유령의 낌새, 느껴져?
That's weird. I thought they'd be here!
이상하네
이런 곳이면 있을 텐데…
Ms. Maria, I should...
마리아 씨, 역시 저…
Ms. Maria? Did she go back?
마리아 씨?
먼저 돌아갔나?
As I was informed. I found you, Thunder Rai.
정보대로다
찾았다, 선더 라이
Who is there?!
누구냐?!
The Dagwon massacre will begin with you!
다그온 몰살의 시작은 너부터다!
You must be Pulse Seijin!
네놈은, 펄스 성인!
Try Dagwon!
트라이 다그온
Thunder Rai!
선더 라이
Thunder Knuckle!
선더 너클!
No Dagwon can defeat me, Pulse Seijin!
아무리 다그온이라 해도
이 펄스 성인을 이길 순 없다!
Don't underestimate me!
얕보지 마라!
It seems that I can't face you with this small display.
이정도의 모니터론 힘을 발휘할 수 없군
The match will continue soon!
승부는 일단 뒤로 미루지!
I really thought it might be a ghost...
틀림없이 유령일 거라고 생각했는데…
Is visiting these places fun?
이런 곳을 견학하는 게 즐겁니?
It is fun!
즐거워요!
An alien came out of the TV?
우주인이 TV에서?
Yes, the Pulse Seijin that I met in the station had special abilities that let him ride on waves and move from one TV to another.
네, 제가 방송국에서 조우한 펄스 성인은 특수한 능력을 지니고 있어서 전파에 타서, TV에서 TV로 이동할 수 있습니다
That's an interesting creature.
헤에, 별난 생물이군요
And it materializes itself inside the TV and attacks.
그리고 TV 안에서 실체화해서 공격해 옵니다
When it gets dangerous for him, he goes back into TV.
위험해지면 다시 TV 속으로 돌아가 버립니다
Feh, you look proud.
쳇, 잘난척 하기는…
Moreover, you went to the TV station with Ms. Maria? I don't like the sound of that.
게다가, 마리아 씨랑 둘이서 방송국에 갔다고? 마음에 안들어
Don't be jealous!
질투하지마
Anyway, Rai, how do you take it down?
그래서 라이 그녀석을 해치울 수단은?
I hope you know, as a detective of the Space Police!
우주 경찰 기구의 형사라면 당연히 알고 있겠지?
Yes!
네!
I'm studying it.
그건 아직 공부중입니다
So, you're saying that an alien that can move among numerous TVs is our opponent?
그렇다면, 무수히 많은 TV를 사용해서 이동하는 우주인이 상대라고?
We can't face such an enemy!
그래선 손 쓸 도리가 없다구
So let's study it together!
그러니까 모두 같이 공부해요
Study, you say...
공부 말이지…
No matter how Ms. Maria or other girls set you up, you're just like that at the end of the day.
뭐야, 마리아 씨나 여자애들이 떠받들어 줘도 결국은 그정도냐?
Our new detective seems incompetent.
신참 형사는 칠칠치 못하시구만
I have something to say about that, Geki senpai,
말이 나와서 말인데요, 게키 선배
That is Ms. Maria following me as she wishes!
그건 마리아 씨가 멋대로 따라오는 거라구요
She's just annoying and doesn't help...
성가시기만 할 뿐
아무것도…
You punk!
이자식!
Are you going to defy your senpai?!
선배에게 반항할 셈이냐?!
If you want to be impertinent, then come back again after taking the alien down yourself!
주제넘은 소리를 지껄이고 싶거들랑 혼자서 우주인을 쓰러뜨리고 와라!
It's not right to fight a comrade!
서로 싸우고 있을 때가 아니야!
Rai, tell us more about Pulse Seijin.
라이, 펄스 성인에 대해 좀 더 자세히 설명해다오
Yes...
네…
Finally...
마침내…
Finally the one with supernatural power I found debuts worldwide!
마침내 내가 찾아낸 초능력자가 전국에 데뷔하는 거야
And then I'll prove that the power isn't a trick or something!
그리고 초능력이 확실한 걸로…!
I win!
이겼다!
Yuusha Shirei
Dagwon
용자지령
다그온
Original Korean Subtitles by Jaebari (재바리)
Translated to English by Subdivers
Checked by Great Exkaiser103
자막 원본(번역): 재바리
수정: Subdivers
Yuusha Shirei
Dagwon
용자지령
다그온
Multimedia Room
시청각 교실
Ms. Yuiko~
케이코 씨~
Hasatoshi!
하사토시 군~
For these two lovers,
사랑하는 두사람을 위해
Super Colon goes on a special sale tomorrow!
슈퍼 코론은 내일 특매합니다!
Alright.
좋아!
Now, come, Pulse Seijin!
자, 와라
펄스 성인!
I'll definitely get you this time!
이번엔 반드시 붙잡아 주마!
Waging the reputation of the Space Police!
우주 경찰 기구의 명예를 걸고!
-Mr. Yuiko~
-Hasatoshi~
-케이코 씨~
-하사토시 군~
You seem ambitious, recruit detective.
의욕이 넘치는군, 신참 형사
It's a dual, Pulse Seijin!
승부다, 펄스 성인!
Do you want to die that much?
그렇게 죽고싶나?
What did you say?!
뭐라고?!
Then come to the Rinkai Gym!
그렇다면 임해 경기장으로 와라
What?
뭐야?
Then I'll face you.
그럼 상대해 주마
Don't be frightened.
겁내지 마라
Rinkai Gym...
임해 경기장…
Rai!
라이!
If you don't hurry up, we'll be late for the live show!
서두르지 않으면 방송에 늦는다구!
Hurry up and go to the TV station...
어서 방송국에…
Huh? Did he leave first?
어레, 먼저 갔나?
No! I'm going to be late!
위험해! 내가 지각하겠어!
If you want to be impertinent, then come back again after taking the alien down yourself!
주제넘은 소리를 지껄이고 싶거들랑 혼자서 우주인을 쓰러뜨리고 와라!
That's right. Geki senpai is correct.
확실히, 게키 선배의 말대로야
So I must...!
그렇기에…!
I see...
과연 그렇군…
There was a reason Pulse Seijin chose this place.
펄스 성인이 이곳을 선택한 이유가 있었군
Hey, will this corner be alright without a rehearsal?
이봐, 이번 코너 리허설 안 했는데 괜찮겠어?
That is, our performers aren't here yet!
그게, 출연자가 아직도 안 온 모양이예요
That's not good...
하아? 그거 위험하잖아
We had difficulties preparing for such a stage!
일부러 이런 무대를 준비해 뒀는데 말이야
Hey! Is Rai ready yet?
이봐! 라이는 아직이야?
I told you it's 4'o clock!
4시라고 내가 말했지?
There's no more time until the live broadcast!
더이상 방송 때까지 시간이 없어!
It's not right...
이상하네…
He must have left earlier than me...
나보다 먼저 출발했을 텐데…
Producer! Are our performers here yet?!
프로듀서! 출연자 안 왔다며?!
What are you going to do?
어떻게 할 거야?!
Oh, I see...
아아, 그렇구나~
What are we going to do?!
이젠 어떻게 해야 하냐구!
You! Think and do something!
자네! 가만히 있지 말고 생각 좀 해봐!
Even if you say so...
나한테 그런 소릴 해봤자…
Rai, please come quick!
라이도 참, 빨리 좀 오라구!
Now, come! Pulse Seijin!
자, 와라!
펄스 성인!
Hey.
여봐
En senpai?!
엔 선배?!
It's not only En.
엔 뿐만이 아니야
I am wasting my fun after-school hours for this...
아아, 즐거운 방과후의 한때가…
It's actually fun here for me!
전 즐거운데 말이죠
You really make lots of trouble.
정말 민폐 끼치는 녀석이구만
Why are you senpais here?
서, 선배들, 어떻게 여기에?
That guy there.
저녀석이야
He was keeping an eye on you.
저녀석이 널 감시하고 있었어
Just in case you go fight as you please when you meet an enemy.
만에하나, 적과 접촉한 네가 멋대로 나서지 않도록 말이지
Ms. Yuiko~
케이코 씨~
Hasatoshi~
하사토시 군~
Is that the alien?
저게 우주인인가요?
Isn't it obvious enough?
그럴 리 없잖냐
It's already 5'o clock! You should have discussed the time...
아아, 벌써 5시잖아
만날 시간부터 정해놓으라구
Alright, let's go!
좋아요, 여러분!
Time for a new Sunset Kiss today!
오늘도 힘차게 선셋 키스~♡
Sunset Kiss?
선셋 키스?
I think I heard that name before...
어디선가 들은 것 같은…
The show has already begun!
방송 시작해 버렸어~!
What should we do? It's our corner and we have nothing!
어떡해! 이제 곧 우리 코너라구!
Even if you ask me...
나한테 어떡하냐고 물어봤자…
I am ruined!
이젠 다 틀렸어!
I'm going to fired if the corner gets spoiled!
코너 망치면 난 잘릴지도 몰라~
I really wonder where that Rai fellow went...
정말 어디 간 걸까?
라이 녀석…
It's not the time to laugh!
웃고 있을 때냐?!
Be responsible! You're the responsible one!
책임 지라구, 책임!
What did you say?!
뭐예요?!
I kept quiet, and now you're talking rude!
가만히 듣고 있자니 말 막 하시네!
You lay all the blame on me, so do you think you're not responsible at all?
전부 남 탓으로 돌리고 당신 책임은 없다 이거야?!
What's up with that language?! Who do you think I am?
뭐야, 그 말투는?! 내가 누, 누구라고 생각하고…
Ads are airing! We can't make it if we don't prepare right now!
CM 들어갔습니다! 이제 준비하지 않으면 못 맞춰요!
My life is over...
끝장이야… 내 인생…
I must use the last means in times like this...
할 수 없지
이렇게 되면…
Back to the Sunset Kiss you were waiting for!
선셋 키스
오래 기다리셨습니다!
Hey, are you sure this is really the right place?
여봐, 정말 여기 맞냐?
Of course, there's no way I'd confuse the places!
어마나~
착각할 리 없잖아요
Now, who'll be here with us?
자, 오늘은 어떤 애가 나올까나~
You're the street corner champion!
당신이 바로 길모퉁이 챔피온!
Kai, let's go back.
카이, 그만 돌아가자
No. Wait until the sun goes down.
안돼, 해질 때까지 기다려
Hey, look! That!
아앗, 이봐, 저거!
Hi!
네에~
I'm Maria Tobe, 16 years old!
토베 마리아, 16살입니다~
I forgot!
까먹고 있었다!
So, Maria, what'll you do today for us?
그래서, 마리아
오늘은 뭘 보여줄 거지?
I'll sing a song!
네, 노래를 부를게요
The title is "Tomorrow will be clear."
제목은 "내일은 맑겠지"
I'll do my best to sing, so I hope you all like it!
열심히 부를테니까
여러분, 잘 부탁해요~
I counted the number of clouds, lying in the blue sky
푸른 하늘에 드러누워서 구름을 세었어
"I'll join," you said, and you gazed upon the sky too
「같이 할게」라며 너도 하늘을 바라보았지
Ms. Maria, you're awesome!
마리아 씨, 멋져요~
Stretching and breathing deep, I met the wind...
등을 펴고 심호흡하며 바람을…
I found you!
여기 있었구나!
You finally came, Pulse Seijin!
드디어 왔군, 펄스 성인!
What were you doing? You're late!
뭐하다 왔냐, 늦었잖아!
You are the ones who were waiting at the wrong place!
만날 장소를 착각한 건 그쪽이잖아!
What?!
뭐야?
You told that we'll meet at Rinkai Gym!
임해 경기장이라고 했잖아!
-Hey.
-Ye- yes?
-이봐…
-네, 네;;?
This is Rinkai Stadium.
여기는 임해 스타디움
Rinkai Gym is...
임해 경기장은 말이지…
the next building!
저 옆이라구!
Unforgivable!
용서 못한다!
Try Dagwon!
트라이 다그온
Thunder Rai!
선더 라이
It's a bigger alien than we thought.
생각보다 커다란 우주인이구만
Its size must be depending on the size of the display.
아마 TV 모니터의 크기에 따라 몸의 크기도 변할 겁니다
That's right!
그 말대로다!
That structure had a bigger display...
저쪽이 더 큰 모니터였는데…
Unforgivable, Thunder Rai!
용서 못한다, 선더 라이!
Not only did you mess with my plan, but you also brought your comrades!
계획을 엉망으로 만든데다가 동료까지 데려오다니!
No. Your opponent is only me!
아니, 너의 상대는 나 혼자다!
Then combine at once!
그럼 얼른 합체해라!
I must see Ms. Maria!
마리아 씨를 봐야 한다구!
I know already.
정말, 알았어요
Merging Fusion!
융합합체
(融合合體)
Dag Thunder!
다그 선더
Let's go, Pulse Seijin!
간다, 펄스 성인!
Bolt Shoot!
볼트 슛!
Do you think you can defeat me with that weak attack?
그정도의 공격으로 날 해치운다고?
Don't make me laugh!
웃기는구만!
One hit and you're dead!
이제 한 발만 먹이면 끝이다!
Die!
죽어라!
Wh- what?!
아, 아니?!
This ends now, Pulse Seijin!
이걸로 끝이다, 펄스 성인!
I see. That guy won't be fed any energy or able to run away without a TV display.
그렇구나, TV 모니터만 없어지면 녀석은 에너지 공급도
도망치지도 못합니다
Damn you!
이놈아!
Rai! You will finish this!
라이, 끝장은 네가 내라!
Yes sir, Ryu senpai!
네, 류 선배!
Come here, Thunder Shuttle!
Come here, 선더 셔틀
Thunder Fusion!
뇌명합체
(雷鳴合體)
Thunder Dagwon!
선더 다그온
Thunder Dagwon...
선더 다그온!
Let's go, Pulse Seijin!
간다, 펄스 성인!
I'll make you eat all the energy I accumulated until now!
지금까지 모은 에너지를 모두 먹여주마!
No problem!
이딴 것 쯤!
Wha-?!
아니?!
Moon Cutter!
문 커터!
Thunder Lancer!
선더 랜서!
Lancer Finish!
랜서 피니시!
Thank you, everyone!
감사합니다, 여러분~
Thank you very much!
성의 감사드려요~
What a relief! I won't be fired thanks to this.
다행이야 이걸로 안 짤리게 됐어
Truly a relief...
정말 다행이야
I don't think I hate this.
이런 것도 나쁘진 않네
Well, I guess publicizing Rai can be done when my research is over...
뭐, 라이의 선전은 내 연구가 끝난 뒤에 하면 되고…
Please overlook!
그, 그만 봐주세요
Shut up! If you came to the right location, it could have ended much earlier!
시끄러! 네가 장소만 안 틀렸어도 훨씬 잘 됐을 거라구
I guess it's alright now. We were able to take a look at Rai's new fusion!
이제 됐잖냐 라이의 새로운 합체도 볼 수 있었고 말이야
Thunder Dagwon...
선더 다그온이라…
It was definitely awesome.
확실히 대단했습니다
He took him down by himself.
혼자서 해치웠고…
It's because Ryu senpai helped me.
류 선배가 도와준 덕이지만요
Because of that I couldn't see the splendor of Ms. Maria!
그것 때문에 마리아 씨의 화려한 모습을 못 봤다구!
Hey, you-!
이봐…!
Hey, let him go and forgive him.
이봐, 적당히 용서해 줘라
Congratulations on your first victory, Thunder Rai.
첫 승리를 축하한다
선더 라이
It was a wonderful show.
제법 즐거운 쇼였다
But, next time, we'll make it more interesting.
하지만 다음부터는 더 즐겁게 해다오
Who are you?!
누구냐?!
You must be that...
너는 그 때의…!
Hido!
히도!
We, the Three Warugaia Brothers, took Sargasso.
사르갓소는 우리 와르가이아 3형제가 접수했다
We are different from those incompetent fools before.
우리는 지금까지의 별볼일 없는 놈들과는 격이 달라
What did you say?!
뭐라고?!
We'll definitely take your necks!
그 목, 반드시 따갈 테니까 말이지
You'd better be prepared, Dagwon gentlemen.
각오해 둬라, 다그온 제군
Three Warugaia Brothers?
와르가이아… 3형제라고?!
The sun suddenly called me
태양이 갑작스레 나를 불러내서
taiyou ga fui ni ore wo izanau
To come to the blue sea
푸르게 비치는 바다로 만나러 갔지
aoku sukitooru umi ni ai ni kita
The ripples are coming and going
밀려왔다 돌아가는 잔물결
yosete wa kaesu sazanami
An endless melody
멈추지 않는 멜로디
tomaru koto nai MELODY
To keep that shape for eternity
그 모습을 영원히 유지할 수 있도록
sono sugata towa ni tsunagu you ni
I'll follow the fate of the dream
꿈의 행방을 뒤쫓아 갈 거야
oikakete yuku yo yume no yukue
Sparkling far away
멀리서 반짝이던
tooku kirameita
A Prism in the Wind
바람 속의 프리즘
kaze no naka no PRISM
Yuusha Shirei
Dagwon
Preview for Next Episode
용자지령
다그온
차회예고
Finally, the Three Warugaia Brothers took Sargasso and started to create unrest!
마침내 와르가이아 3형제가 사르갓소의 지배하며 불안한 행동을 시작했다!
From now on. the aliens' attacks will become more and more violent.
이제부터 점점 우주인들의 공격은 격해져 가겠지
That punk came out. The enemy this time is Trucker Seijin!
나타났어, 이번 적은 트럭커 성인이다
A car type alien that simply runs no matter what!
오로지 끊임없이 달리는 자동차 형태의 우주인!
Rai's following him, but will it be alright?
라이가 추적하고 있지만 괜찮을까?
Let's leave this to Thunder Rai for now!
여기는 일단 선더 라이의 솜씨대로 하자
Next time on Yuusha Shirei Dagwon! Chase the Ghost Truck!
다음회 용자지령 다그온
유령 트럭을 쫓아라
Do not let your guard down, Thunder Dagwon!
방심하지 마라, 선더 다그온!
Chase the Ghost Truck!
유령 트럭을 쫓아라